BGM
Here we go!
This time I'm joined by Rei Inoue of JuiceJuice
and Yoshio Sato of Beyond Seasonings.
This show is about the behind-the-scenes of the production of various artists
This is a program that goes behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I, Inoue, after all...
Bus tour recently!
JuiceJuice went to Izu for an overnight bus tour.
At the last live, there was a surprise from the fans!
Mr. Uemura is about to graduate.
A representative of the fans came to the front and read a letter to Mr. Uemura.
And the point that made me cry was
Wonderful World.
Everyone sang the song instead of us.
I was crying all the time looking at the screen thinking that was not fair.
I was crying all the time looking at the screen thinking that it was not fair, but the singer herself was so happy that she was more happy than moved.
And some of the junior members were crying.
I was really impressed with Mr. Kamimura.
And the fans, too.
It was a night that made me realize that there are many things that can be conveyed only by talking directly with fans like this.
But you've never done the Beyoncé buster before.
That's right.
We've been saying for 5 years that we want to do it together, but we've never done it.
We love to communicate with our fans.
We love to communicate with our fans, so we would love to play the buster!
Please, adults!
Please do.
Yes, I'm Satoyoshi.
I was a guest of Mimosa at Hello Project's trainees' presentation in March 2024.
Beyoncé's major debut is in 2019.
I performed at the trainee presentation within the year of their major debut.
It's been a while.
Yes, it has.
To the teachers who were watching us when we debuted.
It's been a while since they've seen us perform.
Everyone was really fired up.
The students who have already been trainees
as they did when they were trainees.
The audition group also went back to the basics.
They wanted to stand out the most.
Like, "Let's be the biggest dancer.
That kind of fighting spirit.
They were all very competitive.
It's been almost five years since my debut.
I'm very happy to have had this opportunity to go back to the basics.
That's important.
I don't know...
There's a sense of tension that only first-time students can feel.
I'm sure there are people who have a lot of tension.
I'm sure there are some of you out there.
I'd like you to pay attention to the expressions on the members' faces.
I'd like you to pay attention to the expressions of the members who have different feelings at each show.
Now, let's start from here.
Tsubaki Factory's recording of the song "Atashi Rhythm
Here is the recording of the guitar and bass for Tsubaki Factory's song "Atashi Rhythm".
Music
DEFI
Is it good?
Amineki's eyes
But I can't even replace them
I want to believe
This is me, this is me, this is me, this is me
If you keep the rhythm going
I've got it, I've got it, I've got it, I've got it
How wonderful
I've been looking for love from someone else too
Squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak
I can't stop the beat
Give me your hand
I could be you if I wanted to be you
Thank you for watching!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
The direction is much better!
The difference in passion between the two of you is really interesting.
Opposite styles.
Quite an interesting production.
But it was good.
It was really good.
If you're ready.
Yes, sir!
Yes, please.
But I can't replace anyone.
I want to believe.
This is it, this is it, this is it...
Dance to a new rhythm.
Now Dance Five
Somehow...
Next rock ship
More than anyone
I want to dance and stop
Listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me
I...
I'll never stop
Even here
Somehow, someway...
I'm going to be me.
This is me, this is me, this is me, this is me
As long as I dance to the rhythm
I'd be smiling
I'd be like so many of myself I'd have to admit there's a reason
Listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me
I'm the light and the dark
Words aren't easy to say, so I'm trying to make the most of them
I've been through a lot of bad days
I'm going to be me, just like that, just like that
Subtitle: Kiyo Hiyo
Isn't this song really good? I feel like it's coming together.
It's coming together, huh?
Well, in a good way.
Mr. Watanabe, can't you just keep it up from the third chorus on?
You want to take it away?
Can I save the pattern of making things crazy and exciting?
Okay, the 3rd chorus.
My body is still warm.
I can't replace anyone.
I want to believe.
This is it, this is it, this is it, this is me
If you dance to the rhythm
I knew this sound
I'd rather be myself for a minute
I wish I could step into someone else's shoes
Listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me, listen to me
I'm sure you're right.
I don't know. I don't know.
It's not easy... but we have to take care of it.
I've had a lot of bad days.
And that's how you become me.
〜ED.
ED.
Isn't it cool?
Then the ending solo... Arturo solo.
It's nice, but it's starting to smell good.
Kiku... you should have more of a crying feeling...
It's good.
The notes are delicious here.
Yes, yes...
Yes, it's like it suddenly becomes sad.
In that way, you gradually become me.
It becomes me.
I think it's perfect.
I'd like to start with "Doon".
Okay. Okay.
Let's do it.
But it's perfect. Let's wrap it up with this.
I was thinking that a longer doon at the beginning would be good, too.
I think it might be interesting to stay here for a night and a half.
Music
Cool!
Thank you very much!
The arrangements are usually cool, and the structure of the music,
The bass guitar is pretty much a blah blah blah all the way from start to finish.
I'm a little tense.
I started from the point of making a song that would get people excited at a live performance,
I think it will be a lot of fun at a live performance.
The sound was recorded with great sound.
Listen to the guitar sound.
Arrangement-wise, it's just so exciting,
I want everyone who has just started playing a musical instrument to imitate this.
I hope that everyone who is just starting to play an instrument will try to imitate this,
Please try it.
Please play the video of me playing it.
Please play the video of me trying to play it.
It's a really cool arrangement. It was really cool.
When we sing, we usually sing along with the music,
I try to sing as if I were an instrument,
But when I actually listen to the music, there are a lot of parts that I think are better to listen to,
The way he was enjoying playing was really cool, and the bass guitar was very detailed.
The bass guitar was very detailed. I was really surprised to hear how much detail they put into the bass guitar.
But he seemed to be having so much fun that it made me want to do nothing at all.
I'm sorry.
What was it?
I heard this song "Atashirhythm" at the winter Halo Project concert tour,
I've been listening to this song "Atashirhythm" with 3 of us, and the intro of this song makes me throw up BEYOND,
OH!
The intro was so cool that I could throw up in a cool way,
It was so cool that I could throw up in a cool way, and it was a lot of fun to see the backstage of such a song,
It was a lot of fun to see how they recorded the song, and I could see that they made many fine adjustments to the instruments,
Yes, it was very interesting.
It was very interesting.
That's all for Tsubaki Factory Atashirhythm Instrument Recording.
Thank you for your work.
Next up, here we go... Angulum Red Line Vocal Recording.
Here's a look at the vocal recording of Redline Hiro Yamayoki from Angulum's latest single, "Redline.
All right, let's get some shots then.
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Four seconds.
I wonder if I'm allowed to be an idiot.
I'll be on the next bus. I want to go home.
I like your voice and your expression.
I'd like to sing a little bit more of the melody.
I'd like to unify the melody.
I wonder if it's okay if I'm being silly.
I'm thinking this way and that way, and it's coming on the next pass.
That's why the melody is...
Dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah-dah.
Dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah dah
I wonder if I'm allowed to be an idiot
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's what it feels like.
I hope we can keep doing that.
OK!
Okay, let's go across the street.
I'm wondering if it's okay to be silly.
I'm taking the moon bus. I just want to go home.
Okay.
Let's continue.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes. - Yes.
Is it true that I missed you?
I'm not being honest, but I'm unconsciously taking precautions.
Yes, um, I feel good. This is also what I was saying earlier.
It's like ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
So there's not much more nuance there.
Well, a database is also a database, so...
It's hard to say "database,
Well, not at all.
I want you to sing with a little bit of that in the groove, though.
OK, let's try it again.
I wonder if it's true that I missed you in the beta-based work.
I've missed you so much in my beta-based work.
Okay, let's see what we can do.
Okay, let's go there.
Oh, that's good.
Tajiyou.
Yes, that's good.
That's the way it's going to be.
Yes.
Raise, see in one shot.
Yes, sir.
Okay?
Okay.
Okay, then, you can go for a rap or a tear-off,
Let's rap, please.
Let's rap!
Let's start with the part where you say it's appropriate, and then we'll go into it with more gusto.
Yes, sir.
Listen, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
What's your excuse for saying that people are just doing it for your own good?
Yes, I've been troubled, I've been struck by today's issue
What's your excuse for being a person, what's your sense of humor, let's get to the arcade game, let's get to the music!
Yes, I'll be the first to say it, what's your excuse for being a person, what's your sense of style, let's do it for you.
I'm going to sing myself to sleep till àποbsp leave to wearanakaman
mogą
enj sweep
do only you é
ي
I can't do it, but I want to make a good amount of music here.
I can't do it, but I want to make a good amount here.
I want to make a song that says, "That's right, that's right, that's right..." and I want to keep making it.
Love, love, love just for you, come on, come on, come on, yes!
What a nonsense excuse, it's for your sake, I'm a nonsense
I want to cross the red line, I want to get hurt, I want to hurt you
I do I do I break my love's body and go on
I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do
I do I do I'll only show you the red line
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you.
Yes, I've been saying...
I've been saying that your voice fits this song "Red Line
Yuki's voice suits the song "Red Line" very well.
I think your voice fits this song "Red Line" very well.
The A melody is cool and the rap part is a little bit innocent.
and the gap between the cool A-melody and the innocent rap
I thought the gap between the cool A melody and the innocent rap is really nice.
I was thinking how carefully she sings.
I was thinking that she sang with great care.
Yuki-chan has a core, but she has a strong sense of receptivity.
I heard her core but receptive voice.
I was listening to her voice, and I thought it was really wonderful.
I was thinking that the part of the chorus
I thought it would be really difficult to sing the chorus
But you did it so beautifully.
It was so beautiful.
I wondered if it was a good fit.
I really like the way you sing the high part in your own voice.
I really like the way you go high with your own voice.
It's like you have the ability to release heat.
I also like the way you give off heat.
I'll be listening to you from now on.
I'd like to get a better chair
I would like to listen to it more often.
That's all for the red line of Anjelm
This is Yuki Hirayama's vocal recording.
I'll be rooting for you anytime.
Keep up the good work!
Rei Inoue of Juice Juice and
Yoshinobu Sato Utano of Beyonce Seasonings presents Apkami
Here is the next one!
Juice Juice Wonderful World
2023 Juice Juice Version Vocal Recording
From Juice Juice's latest album
Wonderful World 2023 Juice Juice Version
Please take a look at Risa Irie's vocal recording
Yes, sir.
So, let's start with the chorus.
This world is wonderful, isn't it?
me
goo I think it's Gara
How's high school? 1 for high school and 4 for 4?
I'm going to go with the low part, but I'm a bit of a lullaby, so I'm just going to sing it here, but in a cheerful way.
Let's get on with it... but I'd like to see more of you.
It's a wonderful world, isn't it?
goo me
Goo me!
ok, so you can't go from the raw sea to the hole with that hard time...
You say love me
And I say love you
Only you forever
Subtitle Kiminomiya
The Two of Us
Now, you're saying it all in your back voice
I'll say it in half.
And then you're right.
The part where you're saying it in your own voice...
I can say it a lot more clearly.
Thank you for watching!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Then let's sing it as it is, with a pretty and sparkling feeling.
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's try one more time.
Please do.
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
we
th
Gutan ni nani no 6
ال-
I'm not here.
I felt like my body was just going to flow like this... and then I felt a rustle... and that's when I should have taken it.
Me.
I think I practiced this last part...
Shop Lu
So I'm going to go there for a bit.
Yeah, OK.
The chorus part at the top.
I thought I'd fill it out with the chorus.
I'm thinking of filling it in with the chorus.
I think I'm going to go up there.
Yeah, OK.
Okay, let's go to the next one.
If you're here, if I think of you
That's all it takes to make this place a wonder follower
Yeah, that was close.
But it's all starting to make sense now.
When I think of you
Yes, yes, yes
Thank you
Yes, OK
Yes, uh, then this is more than a song, right?
Yes.
The album version of "Wanderlust World" has a completely different chorus.
The orchestra is different in places, but Juice Juice has twice as many members as the original.
So, I think that's the reason for the thickness of the voices and the ability to use different pitches when we harmonize.
I feel like you are presenting the current JuiceJuice.
I thought it was a very chic arrangement as I was recording the song.
The original Wonderful World has a magnificent worldview, so I guess it's different from the original Wonderful World, and I love both of them.
I love them both!
Yes, um...
The original
Yes...
I've been listening to Wonderful World since I was in junior high school.
I see.
I've been listening to it since I was a junior high school student.
I really want to hear it live, the sound pressure is so powerful.
Risa-chan also sang the difficult hammory carefully, carefully, carefully, carefully, one note at a time.
I'm looking forward to seeing BEYONDZ re-record some of the songs from their debut one day.
I hope we can continue to do so for a long time.
That's all for Juice Juice Wonderful World 2023 Juice Juice Ver. Vocal recording of Risa Irie!
Tea no oma! First album Channel 1 is now on sale!
Today, I had a good thing.
It's time to say goodbye to Apkami, brought to you by Inaume Late Satoyoshi Utano!
Now, we have seen various videos this time again.
I, Satoyoshi, was very much impressed by the instrumental recording.
I was very impressed by the instrumental recordings, and some of the members of Miyons took pictures of the recordings.
I'm always looking forward to seeing the instrument recordings.
I always look forward to seeing the instrument recordings.
It was a lot of fun to see such cool footage.
The upside for me is that we record the instruments after they have been filmed.
I'm looking forward to seeing the recording of the instruments.
I'm looking forward to seeing more recordings in the future.
I thought I could develop my ear to listen to the orchestra a little more.
I also thought it would be fun to see the members' singing habits.
I'm really looking forward to seeing it.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I thought it was a lot of fun to watch.
In this episode, we'll be going behind the scenes of the production of the various artists who belong to the Upfront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally get to see.
This time upcami's partner is JuiceJuice's Innovate!
This time's up-camera partner was Yumomo Satoyoshi of BEYOND'S SIZENINGS!
Good bye.
Next time on Upcame: Tsubaki Factory's recording of "Atarizumu"!
And Morning Musume。23 wake up call Wake up when you wake up recording will be released!
Please look forward to it!
Thank you for watching!